Guide to the Media Services records, [ca. 1950-2015.]
Media Services records, [ca. 1950-2015]
- Series IV. Videotapes
  - Subseries IVa. Videotapes transferred from Distributed Learning Services
    - Bio Diversity, Baldhill, Woodland Birds, Interview, OFC-314, June 16, 1995; V-3804; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Bio Diversity, Baldhill, Woodland Birds, OFC315, June 16, 1995; V-3805; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Bio Diversity, Bob-A-link, Field Bird, OFC-316, June 16, 1995; V-3806; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Bio Diversity, Bob-A-link, Field Bird, OFC-317, June 16, 1995; V-3807; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - 4-H Camp Wabasso, 1A, OFC318, August 15, 1995; V-3808; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - unidentified, V-3809; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Eng. Opening seg. #1 TC/CT (no case), January 12, 1990; V-3810; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - AA: Admirals Club Podcast, DVD-550; DVD (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - AG - HVX200 Countdown, 2005; DVD-551; DVD (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Antigone, Expo Tame, October 9, 2003; V-3811; V - DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Edit Master 6, Antigone - Tape Version, August 18, 2003; V-3812; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Apples-Cancer Interview & B-Roll, February 24, 2005; V-3813; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Arts Alliance, Susan Woods, Audio, October 10, 2002; V-3814; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Malcolm Bilson, Cornell U., Hungary, Teranex Conversion Pal to NTSC, Educational Television CTR, July 9, 2004; V-3815; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - BCERF, Barbour Warren, "Diet, Lifestyle and Breast Cancer Risk", 52:30, Web Master, March 17, 2004; V-3816; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - BCERF, Suzanne Snedeker, Web Presentation, "Why is There Concern?", V-3817; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Fall B-Roll, Campus, Arts Quad, October 2001; V-3818; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Chemistry Raw, V-3819; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Student Interviews, Chemistry CD Students, T-1, June 6, 2003; V-3820; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Clean Room, September 25, 2003; V-3821; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - CPL - Virginia Riemirski Lecture, Login: Computer Logs and Education, October 4, 2002; V-3822; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Copy Right and Library Services, ATC, Student-Assist. T-1, V-3823; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Cornell Beauty Shots, Cornell Campus Stock Footage, V-3824; V - DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Cornell News Clips, Students Cutting, 2007; V-3825; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Cornell University, College of Engineering, Accelerating Innovation to Transform the Future, DVD-552; DVD (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Cow Footage EYH, V-3826; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Diversity Candidate, Debra Richardson, 104 Sage Hall - Ramin Room, May 13, 2008; V-3827; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - The ?KE Challenge, Master, V-3828; V - DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - The ?KE's, Don Weadon Various Intv: George Nesterczuk '66, Lyn Davidson '71, Frank Pinter '71, JL/BR, October 13, 2001; V-3829; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - DL Expo, Tape 1, January 16, 2003; V-3830; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - DL Expo, Tape 2, V-3831; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Eames/sHeyely, TV, January 08, 2004; V-3832; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Early Childhood Mentoring Round Table, November 13, 2000; V-3833; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Early Childhood Mentoring, Spencer Road Daycare, March 29, 2001; V-3834; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Early Childhood Mentoring, IC3, May 23, 2001; V-3835; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Early Childhood Mentoring, Melody's Class, March 28, 2002; V-3836; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Early Childhood Mentor, Isabel Interview, April 16, 2002; V-3837; V - 5"3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - One on One, Two by Two, Early Childhood Mentor Project, Master, V-3838; V - DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - One on One, Two by Two, Early Childhood, Mentor Project, Master, V-3839; V - 3.8"2.5" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - One on One, Two by Two, Early Childhood, Mentor Project, Master, November 2, 1999; V-3838 (Box 35-14-3773 - 71)
    - Econ 101 - Frank, Class 4, Reuse, October 1, 2001; V-3840; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Engaging Youth in Urban Greening, Dubbing Master, (Dubbed from Media 100), 471, April, 2003; V-3841; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Engineering in the Real World, Alex Evans, #2064, March 27, 2003; V-3842; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Falling Weight Deflectemeter on Road, (16x9), November 5, 2008; V-3843; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Football Spots (Colgate), 1x3:00, 1x1:00, 5x:30, September 29, 2001; V-3844; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Global Nomads: Cultural Bridges for the New Millennium Master, May 15, 2001; V-3845; V - DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - GI Reel, July 2004; V-3846; V - DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Dr. Soule, Hillside Children's Center, TCI Video, Client: Martha Holden, March 14, 2001; V-3847; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Hotel School Food Service Game, Tape #1, October 1, 2002; V-3848; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Hotel School Food Service Game, Tape #2, October 2, 2002; V-3849; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Hotel School CD - ROM, Steven Weidner, October 8, 2003; V-3850; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Hotel School Restaurant Management, Accountant, December 11, 2002; V-3851; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Hotel School CD-ROM, Steven Weidner, October, 6-7, 2003; V-3852; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Vejoy - Hotel School CD-ROM, Steve Weidner, V-3853; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Loehr - Briggs, Illegal Immigration Debate, June 17, 2004; V-3854; V- 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Industrial Labor Relations, Exterior shot of building, April 23, 2007; V-3855; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - IDSP Scratch 3, V-3856; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - #1 Int 1 + 2 FL, V-3857; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Katzenstein Project, Introduction, Mary Katzenstein, Tape #1, V-3858; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Katzenstein Project, Tape #2, V-3859; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Katzenstein, Proj. Tape #3, V-3860; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Mary Katzenstein, Tape #1, 3 Shoots, Office Last Guest, In Office, V-3861; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Tape #2, 3 Shoots, 1) Office, 2) Classroom, V-3862; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Tape #3, 1) Class 2) Class Guest Lecturer, V-3863; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Class in, "ok…Fox Butterfields talk" At out: Minus one miw.", V-3864; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Tape #5, 1) Office, 2) Class Guest Lecturer, November 7, 2002; V-3865; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Tape #6, 1) Class, 2) Office, 3) Final Class, Guest Lecturer Charles LeCount, November 19, 2002; V-3866; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Isaac Kramnick, Hollis Auditorium, Goldwin Smith Hall, #27084, 17, April 1, 2008; V-3867; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - French Law in Action #2, Paris, PAe 2, Int. #2, Continue (Roger Erraen), #3 Pascal Patitcollor, #4 Denis Bensuede, February 10, 2004; V-3868; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Mastodon in John Chiment, Tape 2, PIEI, October 9, 2001; V-3869; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Merlot - Gerry Henley, March 22, 2003; V-3870; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Wet Mount Prep and Slide Staining,, Micro Biol., June 25, 2008; V-3871; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Susceptible to Kindness: Miss Ever's Boys, The Tuskegee Syphilis Study, 47:00, V-3872; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Miscellany: leadership policy, innovations - Arts Alliance, DL Expo - loop, Gargarino, Nash - wine appreciation, November 2002; V-3873; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Mudge Grafting, Etching Demo, Trot, Edit Master #5, May 19, 2005; V-3874; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - NCRI: Adventures in Living & Learning, Cornell Univ., 2005; DVD-554; DVD (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Net Neutrality, October 2, 2006; V-3875; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Outdoor Life Assembly of Beta Stuff, June 29, 2004; V-3876; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - PAR - Garden Mosaics, Marianne Kiasny, May 21, 2001; V-3877; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Paw Print Anniversary WSH; Risley Catherine March Lunch/Discussion, October 13, 18, 2000; V-3878; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Physics Lab Demo, January 10, 2008; V-3879; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Physics Lab, March 20, 2008; V-3880; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Physics Lab Demos, April 30, 2008; V-3881; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Physics 207, Lab Demos, Mat. Liepe Shoot, November 14-16, 2007; V-3882; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Physics 207, Lab Demos, Mixture 28 & 29, November 26, 2007; V-3883; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Physics 207, Lab Demos, November 30, 2007; V-3884; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Physics 207, Lab Demos, December 5, 2007; V-3885; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Physics 207, Lab Demos, March 21, 2008; V-3886; V- 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Physics 207, Lab Demos, April 24, 2008; V-3887; V-5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Prisons: A Speakers Series, "Drug Courts: Alternatives to Incarceration", Judge John Rowley, Ithaca City Drug Court, February 9, 2000; V-3888; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Prisons: A Speakers Series, "Behind-the Walls - Baccalaureate: Elmira Correctional Facility", Steve Coffman, novelist & former staff Corning & Keuka College Prison Program, Lecture 2, February 16, 2000; V-3889; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Prisons: A Speakers Series, An Interview with Kenneth McClane, Jr., WEB DuBois Proffessor of Literature/English, February 23, 2000; V-3890; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Prisons: A Speakers Series, "The Reinstitutionalization of the Mentally Ill", Tom Terizzi, Director, Prisoner Legal Services of New York, March 1, 2000; V-3891; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Prisons: A Speakers Series, "Race, Crime, Politics", Professor Mark Mauer, #6, April 26, 2000; V-3892; V -5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Ringin g Changes, Dub Master, 452, V-3893; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - President Skorton, "Marshal Plan", Global Capacity Building, Cornell Cast, S.R. # 27201, February 14, 2008; V-3894; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Social Science, Final Project Lecture, April 25, 2007; V-3895; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Steve Hotel Clips, V-3896; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Tapestry - Segment in Progress, March 15, 2007; V-3897; V - DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Theate Arts Spot - "Picasso at the Lapin Agile" [sic], October 16, 2006; V-3898; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Toxicology Lab, Cornell Vet Med, Pet Food Testing, March 28, 2007; V-3899; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - The Transition to Organic, Master, Note: Audio drops out (Do not use), V-3900; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Troubled Youth Intervention, TCI, Cam 1, Tape 1, December 1, 2000; V-3901; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Troubled Youth Intervention, Cam 2, Tape 1, TCI, December 1, 2000; V-3902; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Vet College, Feline Spay, Dr. Harris, For Fig, Jodi Korich, T-2, July 2, 2003; V-3903; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Vet College, Feline Spay, Dr. Harris, For Fig Jodi Karich, T-2, July 2, 2003; V-3904; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Zellman Weuhoff; Chiment - Dinosaur; Hudler - Great Moments, Frankenstein, Hubbell/Ullberg, Edit Master 2, March, 2002, May, 2002; V-3905; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - FWD calibration video, circa early 1990's, 1990s; CD-623; CD-ROM (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - #5, #3, V-3906; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - FWD WM, DVD-553; DVD (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - 2 unidentified White, CD-624 - CD-625; CD-R (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - 6 unidentified, V-3907 - V-3912; V - 5"x3" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - 1 unidentified, V-3913; V - DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Unidentified, ZD-4; ZIP Drive (Box 35-14-3773 - 52)
    - Eng. Quad, Beauty(?) Tape #2, CF01, January 8, 1990; V-3914; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - I.C. From Lib. Slope, CF02, July 8, 1991; V-3915; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Hum. Ec. Playground Tape #1, CF03, November 23, 1991; V-3916; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Clock Tower from Barton Tower, CF04, August 21, 1991; V-3917; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Hum. Ec. B-roll ftg. "Assoc. for Students of Color Ice Cream Social," (wild sound only) Jon Hilton, videographer, CF05, September 9, 1992; V-3918; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Cornell Lax, "Tradition," 1B, CF06, May 2, 1992; V-3919; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Cornell Lax, "Tradition," 1A, CF07, May 2, 1992; V-3920; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Cornell Tradition, Moakley House, Tape 1, CF09, May 22, 1992; V-3921; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Cornell Tradition, Moakley House, Tape 2, CF10, May 22, 1992; V-3922; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Cornell Tradition, Pizza Party (Jabon), CF11, September 16, 1992; V-3923; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Tradition, Football Game Tape #2, CF12, October 31, 1992; V-3924; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Tradition, Football Party, Tape #1, CF13, October 31, 1992; V-3925; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Cornell Trad. Costume Shop, Cam. #1, Tape #3, CF25, May 27, 1989; V-3926; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Hum. Ec., Andrea Parrot in studio, CF26, March 16, 1988; V-3927; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - CU Nursery School, CF29, April 29, 1988; V-3928; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Cornell Stock, Snow General Art Quad, CF30, Winter 1989; V-3929; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Inside Barton Hall, setting up for an event, CF31, October 22; V-3930; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Snow on campus, CF33, Winter 1987; V-3931; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Campus shots, Tower shot from Lib Slope, CF34, March 21, 1986; V-3932; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - From Barton Hall, roof of campus, CF35, V-3933; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Campus-Spring, Tape #1, some shots by Jon Krunnerman(sp?), CF36, March 30, 1988; V-3934; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Cam #1, Tape #1, Beebe Lake, CF37, May 1, 1988; V-3935; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Beebe Lake, Cam 1, Tape 2, CF38, May 1, 1988; V-3936; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Beebe Lake, Cam 1, Tape 3, CF39, May 1, 1988; V-3937; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - CF40, V-3938; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - CF41, V-3939; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - CF42, V-3940; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Beebe Lake, Cam 1, Tape 7, CF43, May 1, 1988; V-3941; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Beebe Lake, Cam 1, Tape 8, CF44, May 1, 1988; V-3942; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Beebe Lake, Cam 1, Tape 9, CF45, May 1, 1988; V-3943; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Beebe Lake, Cam 2, Tape 1, CF46, May 1, 1988; V-3944; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Front Label-[Forest Decline Reel #6, Roots/Lab], [January 15, 1988] or [September 14, 1990]; V-3945; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - (Box 35-14-3773 - Tape Label-{BTI Overview, Building Exteriors})
    - (Box 35-14-3773 - CF47)
    - Beebe Lake, Tape 2, Cam 2, CF57, May 1, 1988; V-3946; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Beebe Lake, Tape 3, Cam 2, CF58, May 1, 1988; V-3947; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Campus map Tape #1, CF59, March 25, 1988; V-3948; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Ben Mintz Cornell Football, 1991 Golf outing, Tape 1 of 3, CF70, August 8, 1991; V-3949; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Bus leaving for China, CF79, December 27, 1988; V-3950; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Irv Chapman intvw w/ Prof. Fisher, CF80, June 22, 1988; V-3951; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Asian Tour Glee Club Rehearsal Sage, Tape #1, CF81, December 23, 1988; V-3952; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - AIP: Akwe:Kon Ext., CF82, November 5, 1991; V-3953; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Awke: Kon Opening, Tape #1, Cam #1, CF83, September 3, 1991; V-3954; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Non-point source-Willsboro 1B, 281, August 3, 1994; V-3955; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Non-point source-Willsboro, 2B, 283, August 4, 1994; V-3956; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Non-point source-Willsboro harvest, tape 1, 284, October 11, 1994; V-3957; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Non-point source-Willsboro farm harvest, tape 2, 285, October 12, 1994; V-3958; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Non-point source-Willsboro farm harvest, tape 3, 286, October 12, 1994; V-3959; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 53)
    - Non-point Source- Lake George, tape 4, 287, October 13, 1994; V-3960; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - My Money, Myself INT08, 288, March 1, 1988; V-3961; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - My Money, Myself Tape #3, INT09, 289, March 1988; V-3962; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - My Money, Myself Tape #4, INT10, 290, March 1988; V-3963; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - My Money, Myself Tape #5, INT11, 291, March 1988; V-3964; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Wetlands Landstrom Landfill, 2 of 3, INT20, 292, July 24, 1990; V-3965; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Wetlands, Fenton, INT21, 293, July 26, 1990; V-3966; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Wetlands, Fenton, #3, INT23, 294, July 26, 1990; V-3967; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Wetlands, Fenton Landfill, INT24, 295, October 8, 1991; V-3968; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Longstroms Landfill, Tape #1, Wetlands, INT25, 296, October 10, 1991; V-3969; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Financial Mgmt. for Older Youth, INT28, 297, September 1, 1992; V-3970; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Financial Mgmt. for Older Youth, INT29, 298, September 1, 1992; V-3971; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Cornell Tradition Program, Cam #1, Tape #2, INT37, 299, May 18, 1987; V-3972; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Cornell Tradition, Tape #4, INT38, 300, June 23, 1987; V-3973; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Cornell Tradition, Tape #2, D.C., INT40, 301, June 23, 1987; V-3974; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Temple of Zeus, Cornell Tradition, INT42, 302, V-3975; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - 4-H Camp #4, interview w/ camp director, INT44, 303, September 10, 1987; V-3976; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Cancer Inst. Tape 4A, part 2 of interview and exteriors, INT53, 305, August 29, 1990; V-3977; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Suburban Deer Damage, 2A, interview w/ DEC official, cutaways of deer crossing road, INT153, 306, April 2, 1993; V-3978; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Animal Science Recruitment, interviews, Lisa Pautler, INT58, 307, April 23, 1992; V-3979; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Mark Thomas, Animal Science Recruit, INT59, 308, May 7, 1992; V-3980; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Animal Science, Steve Walker, Student, INT60, 309, May 7, 1992; V-3981; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Harvest House, tape 7, INT88, 320, V-3982; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Harvest tape, INT89, 321, V-3983; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Harvest, tape 8, INT90, 322, V-3984; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Harvest House, tape 1, INT92, 323, July 30, 1986; V-3985; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - House #1, INT93, 324, July 30, 1986; V-3986; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - INT114, 333, V-3987; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - SACC Elmira Hendy Ave. School, interviews only, 4b, 347, June 7, 1996; V-3988; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - SACC 5A Elmira Hendy Ave. School, B-roll kids in daycare, interview: Kelly Cook, Latchkey teacher, 348, June 7, 1996; V-3989; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - SACC 5B, Interview Kelly Cook cont'd, 349, June 7, 1996; V-3990; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - SACC 6A, Interview Kelly Cook-Latchkey Teacher, kids in program, B-roll kids asking for art supplies, 350, June 7, 1996; V-3991; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - SACC 10A, setting up daycare space demo MVR, 351, July 15, 1996; V-3992; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - SACC 10B, setting up daycare space demo MVR, 352, July 15, 1996; V-3993; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - SACC Clock rolling raw, 11A, 353, V-3994; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - SACC Clock set-up, tear down 11B, 354, V-3995; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - SACC Rose Pandozy open/close, 355, July 24, 1996; V-3996; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - SACC graphics, 356, V-3997; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - SACC 2 1B, King's Elementary Daycare, B-roll, 357, February 27, 1997; V-3998; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Prof Gene German, Kent Maunderville, Hockey, 46, May 3, 1990; V-3999; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Don Greenberg - CSN, October 28, 1991; V-4000; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Roman Watkins, Scholar Athlete, October 21, 1991; V-4001; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Cornell Football Coach Naming, Tape 1, January 14, 1990; V-4002; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Press Conf. New Football Coach, Tape 1, January 15, 1990; V-4003; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - New Football Coach, Press Conference, Tracks B-Roll, Tape 2, January 15, 1990; V-4004; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Brown @ Cornell, Side Line Camera, Tape 1, October 29, 1990; V-4005; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Brown @ Cornell, ESPN, NET Feed, Tape 4, October 27, 1990; V-4006; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 54)
    - Brown @ Cornell, ESPN, NET Feed, Tape 5, October 29, 1990; V-4007; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 55)
    - Cornell/Harvard Football, Top, Tape 2, October 6, 1990; V-4008; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 55)
    - Penn: Field, ESPN, 8 Tapes, November 23, 1989; V-4009 - V-4016; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 55)
    - Transportation, Parking, Story Telling, 6 Tapes, November 8-14, 1990; V-4017 - V-4022; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 55)
    - CCR, "Story Swap", 2 Tapes, November 14, 1990; V-4023 - V-4024; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 55)
    - David Soloman, United Way, November 15, 1990; V-4025; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 55)
    - CCR, Cornell, Chemical Waste Site, November 28, 1990; V-4026; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 55)
    - Home-A-Syst, Fuel Oil Pumping, 185, September 17, 1996; V-4027; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 55)
    - Home Assist, Glen's Kitchen Sink, 186, V-4028; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 55)
    - NPS Pathogens, 1A-6A, 10 Tapes, 187-196, August 14, 1995 - January 9, 1997; V-4029 - V-4038; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 55)
    - Ghiorse Lab, 10A, Dub 196, V-4039; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 55)
    - Pathogens Lab, 10B, 197, November 20, 1996; V-4040; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 55)
    - Pathogens, Skaneateles Water, Treatment Plant, 11A, 198, November 21, 1996; V-4041; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 55)
    - Crypto, May Pick-Up, 199, February 4, 1997; V-4042; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 55)